# Mario Llesta Muñoz

Madrid, Spain · linkedin.com/in/mariollesta · +34 642 77 59 34 · llesta.mario@gmail.com

About 3 years of experience working in IT companies in different roles. Passionate about software development and DevOps methodology. I develop Open Source projects in my GitHub profile.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Gotoeat

Web application for recommendations of places to eat. https://gotoeat.vercel.app/

#### **Portfolio**

Personal portfolio. https://mariollesta-portfolio.dev/

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Madrid, Spain July 2024 – Present

#### OpenNAC Enterprise by Cipherbit (Grupo Oesia)

Software QA Automation

- Performing manual and automated test case and execution tasks on OpenNAC.
- Design and development of a Playwright style guide and best practices for the QA team..
- Design and development of integration, API and E2E tests with Playwright.
- Performing tasks to improve integration and continuous delivery pipelines using Jenkins.
- Use of GitLab and Git for version control of the test developments performed.
- QA reporting and task management using Redmine.

**Madrid, Spain** September 2022 – July 2024

#### **Open Cloud Factory**

Professional Services Specialist

- Support for OpenNAC/EMMA project implementations, including Linux system administration and MySQL/MariaDB database management.
- Automated virtual environment deployments using Ansible playbooks and data analysis with Elasticsearch.
- Management of network access policies, creation of device profiles and technical documentationca.

Madrid, Spain February 2022 – July 2022

#### **NTT DATA Europe & LATAM**

Solution Analyst Intern

- Developed Al-driven software solutions using Multiagent Systems, Java and Spring Boot; deployed and managed systems with Kafka, Kubernetes, PostgreSQL and MongoDB.

## **EDUCATION**

Leganes, Madrid, Spain September 2022

#### **UNIVERSIDAD CARLOS III de MADRID**

Bachelor's Degree in Telecommunication Technologies Engineering
Final Project: Design and development of a serious game in Unity 3D with a predictive model for student assessment, Grade: 9.4/10

# **SKILLS**

- Python FastAPI, Reflex | Javascript React | Tailwind CSS
   PostgreSQL | Linux, Bash scripting | Ansible, Jenkins | Playwright
   Spanish native. Fluent in English.